我说 这电影肯定不是根据真实故事改编的
Ok, in no way is this movie based on a true story.
这绝对会在未来发生
It's a future  true story.
僵尸启示录一定会变成现实的
A zombie apocalypse is going to happen.
要不你以为我为啥像现在这样生活呢?
I mean, why do you think I live the way I do?
嗯 没志向 缺乏自尊心 - 不讲信用
Mm, lack of ambition, no self-respect. Credit score in the ones.
错 是因为僵尸!
No, guys. Zombies!
研究表明我们之中只有一人幸免于难
I mean, studies show only one of us would survive.
问题是...这个人是谁呢?
The question is... Which one?
这取决于生存技巧 你们懂不?
Depends on survival strategy, you know?
就好比我们是反抗他们
It's like are we talking strength to fight them
还是混入其中?
Or ability to blend in and live amongst them?
混入其中?我们现在"混入其中"了么?
Amongst? Are we doing "amongst" now?
嗯哪  - 咱认真点行不?这可是生死攸关
Mm-hmm. Can we focus up here? Okay? This is life and death.
好吧 要说能和僵尸混到一块的，那肯定是戴夫
All right. If we're gonna do ability to blend in, I say Dave.
反正他现在基本也就一僵尸了 -什么?!
He's basically a zombie anyway. What?!
是啊 哥们 我知道你的日程
Yeah, I've seen your daily routine, bro--
早上7点起床 洗澡 吃万年不变的纤维麦片
Wake up at 7:00, shower, eat the same fiber-based cereal
那绝对是中老年妇女的青睐
That is clearly geared towards menopausal women.
人家吃的"嘎嘣脆"是适合所有年龄段的啊
"her choice crunch" is for everyone.
额  -而且和僵尸一样 你没有任何梦想
Eee. And like a zombie, you don't really have any hopes or dreams.
我有梦想!  -真的?
I have dreams! Really?
我还在为我的餐馆梦想而奋斗  -哦 是么
Look, I am still working on opening my own restaurant. Oh, yeah,
貌似六年前你也提过这么档子事
You were just mentioning that, like, six years ago.
是啊 但是我
Yeah, but I de
今晚做了美味的牛排三明治啊
These delicious steak sandwiches for us tonight,
虽然马科斯的烤箱最高只能烧到60度
Despite the fact that Max's oven only goes up to 150.
嗯 如果僵尸入侵 我敢说最先挂的
Well, I could tell you who would die first in a zombie attack.
一定是马科斯
I mean, it's obviously Max.
我吐两次来表明
I did that double spit take to illustrate
你刚刚的话听起来有多蠢
How insane you sound right now.
不好意思 布拉德 可是简会先死  -我?
I'm sorry, Brad, but Jane would die first. Me?
当然  -你身材走样 没有实才
Oh, yeah. You are out of shape, you have no marketable talents,
而且你没有任何生存技能
And you have no survival skills.
相对的 虽然你有你热爱的东西
Counterpoint--there are things in this world that you love.
但你终究会被他们拖累 我的冷酷的内心
That slows people down. My cold, black heart
以及避免我和其他人或物
And living without attachments
产生纠葛 这才是我的优势所在啊
To anyone or anything--it's my greatest asset right there.
别这样 哥们 她真的很好战
Don't do this, dude. She is seriously competitive.
59个热狗
with that 59th hot dog,
小林是目前最具竞争力的大胃王
Kobayashi is now the best competitive eater in the world!
给我准备60个热狗和一个煮蛋定时器
I need 60 hot dogs and an egg timer.
我们开始僵尸之战吧 疯狂的热狗女
Let the zombie Olympics begin, crazy hot dog lady.
尽管放马过来
Bring it on.
各就位 预备 跑!
On your mark, get set, go!
加油啊 亲爱的 超过他
Make it work, baby. Get him, baby.
难道我真的像僵尸?
So I'm really a zombie?
嘿 振作点啊
Hey, you could stand to shake things up a bit.
我知道肉类推销员不是什么理想的工作
I know that selling meat isn't a dream job,
但收入很可观啊 而且它还和餐馆业沾边
But I make good money, it's restaurant-adjacent,
我才刚刚开始喜欢这种小生活
And I just got comfortable taking deuces there.
往好的方面想想
Well, you know, on the bright side,
僵尸现在很火啊
Zombies are super in right now.
那我宁愿做个吸血鬼
I'd rather be a vampire.
哥们 我们都更乐意做吸血鬼
we'd all rather be vampires, bro.
哦!  -啊!
(Jane) ohh! (Max) aah!
搞定! 此时马科斯的脸
Crushed it! Right now Max's face
正被僵尸们啃食呐  -这一局说明不了什么
Is being eaten off by zombies. This is not over between us.
那就放马过来啊
Bring it.
好吧 你现在是我的了 不是么?
Okay, I own you, all right?
我就在你大脑中 而且我拥有3间卧室
I am in your head, and I got a 3-bedroom condo in there
1个大理石台 1个披萨烤箱
With a marble island and a pizza oven
还有一台装满好酒的冰箱!
And a wine fridge!
好了 我们知道了
Okay, we got it.
好吧 不过亲爱的你知道那是我理想中的
Okay, but you do know that that's my dream kitchen,
厨房吧?  -你们...你们就这么走么?
Right, babe? You guys... You guys just go, okay?
我就要飙起来了
I'm about to hit my runner's high.
咱今晚上就出去 我们来大干一场!
We're going out tonight. We're gonna do it big!
幸福终点站
第一季  第07集
==深影字幕组==
我洗衣日的着装实在不想让人看见
My laundry day outfit is not meant for public eyes.
好吧 反正这只是个自助洗衣店
It's all right. It's a laundromat.
来这的都是怪胎
Everyone here's a weirdo.
恩...不是说你
Well... Not... You.
我得换点零钱去
Oh, you know what? I gotta get some quarters.
穿的不错啊
Nice outfit.
哈 你也是 你经常来?
Ha. You, too. So you come here often?
衣服脏的时候才来
Only when mylothes are dirty.
哦 这么一说咱俩还真有共同点
Oh, so we have that in common.
我是托比
I'm Toby.
彭妮
Penny.
这烘干机烘件衣服要N久
You know, these dryers take forever.
去隔壁喝杯咖啡..怎么样?  -嗯...
You... Wanna go next door, get a cup of coffee? Oh, um...
好啊
Sure.
好的
Yeah. Okay.
那份脑子你传真过去没?
Did you fax the brains?
你看见第三区的脑子没?
Did you see the third quarter brains?
上后腰脊肉10美元一磅
Top sirloin's $10 a poun
速冻的 绝对保证营养
It's flash-frozen to retain all the nutrients.
感谢您致电本公司 祝您心情愉快
Thank you for calling trans corps. Have a great day.
我花尽了心思打扮
I spend so much time trying to look good,
结果我穿的邋里邋遢的时候
And then I wear my grungiest outfit,
竟然有帅哥看上我了
And a cute guy is into me.
我以后应该多多光顾自助洗衣店
I should hang out at laundromats more.
虽然要洗一大堆的内衣裤
Yes, I'll have to put up with a lot of abandoned underpants,
但是有偶尔出现的帅哥啊
But every on in a while, cute guy.
款爷在这呢 这不比那些免费的内衣好的多么
Rockefeller over here-- too good for free underpants.
真是等不及让你们见见托比了
I cannot wait for you guys to meet Toby!
天啊 我们简直是志趣相投
Oh, my god. We are into all the same things--
都喜欢家庭购物网 还有网上的宠物宝宝
The home shopping network, baby animals on the internet.
他甚至很欣赏我的刺绣
He even thinks it's cool that I needlepoint.
我说 你是不是在跟我奶奶约会
I gotta tell you, it sounds like you're dating my grandma.
哦 简的短信
Oh, I just got a text from Jane.
她要继续在我脑子里施工?
She's building an addition on the condo she has in my brain?
不带这样的 现在是休战期
Not okay. Not during a recession.
托比来了 他咋还穿成那样?
Toby's here. Why is he still dressed like that?
哦 神啊 你知道他是什么人了吧?
Oh, my god. You know what he is, right?
他是一嬉皮士 -不可能
He's a hipster. Oh, no.
紧身牛仔裤 四季带围巾
The skinny jeans, the scarf no matter the season.
彭妮 这家伙绝对一嬉皮士
This guy's a hipster, penny.
你喜欢的那些东西 他一概藐视  -你胡扯
All those things you like-- he likes them ironically. You don't know that.
我可没有 我站在这就能感受到他的气息
Yes, I do. I can smell him from here, and he smells like
他绝对从跳蚤市场来  -你闭嘴
A flea market. Watch your mouth.
嗨 你收拾好没?
Oh, hey. You ready to go?
听说有个很赞的混音作品的地下交换会
Just heard about this awesome underground mix-tape swap.
马科斯说的对
Max was right.
嘿 那个用来锁自行车的东西
Hey, uh, that bike lock out there--
是你的皮带吧?  -是啊 帅吧?
Is that also your belt? Oh, I know, right?
超帅
Yeah.
嗯...怎么今天这么打扮?
So... What's with the getup?
哦 这个么...
Oh, um... Oh...
这个...
It's, uh... Um...
今天是彭妮的洗衣日
It's penny's laundry day.
你一定很喜欢洗衣服
You must love doing laundry.
我有超强的吸灰能力 浑身上下都是
I really attract stains, you know? All over.
咱走吧  -行 再见
Let's head out. All right. See ya.
很高兴见到你  -我们真的很开心
Nice to meet you. The pleasure is ours.
别紧张哦
Take it easy.
你们说的对
You guys were right.
我就一僵尸
I'm a zombie--
工作时是 和阿莱克斯一起时也是
in my job, with Alex.
她确实是在婚礼上跟你拜拜了
She did literally run away from you at the wedding.
要是有机会你真应该吃掉她的脑子
You shoulda eaten her brains when you had the chance.
是啊 不过 这事过去了就算了 我现在打算
Yeah, but, see, that's it. I'm done. I'm making some
做一些正儿八经的事了 -好啊 挺好的
Serious and aggressive changes in my life. Okay, yeah.
是啊 我29了 我不能在30岁地时候
Yeah. Yeah. I'm 29. I'm not going m30s
还没有任何长进  -必须的!
In the same place I am now. What?
那是一定的啊 哥们
Unh-unh, no, you didn't. Exactly, man.
这也是我辞掉工作的原因
Which is why I'm quitting my job
我要开一家属于自己的餐馆
And I'm opening my own restaurant.
真的?什么?
Really? What?
又来?那谁来付房租?
Come again? Who's gonna pay the rent?
戴夫辞掉工作了?  -别担心 还没呢
Dave quit his job? Don't worry. Not yet.
但他是下定了决心了
But he's definitely going to.
可是戴夫不是那样的人啊 得有人告诉他
Well, that's not like Dave, so someone needs to tell him
那样的决定糟透了
That's a horrible idea.
他有一屁股的债 而且现在经济还那么不景气
He has tons of debt, and the economy sucks.
你怎么能告诉一个男人要他放弃梦想?
How can you tell a man not to follow his dream?
我知道另外一个怀揣梦想的--
I know another man that had a dream--
"美国鼠谭"里的伟福  你会给伟福说
Fievel--in "an american tail." are you gonna tell fievel
他去不了西部了?
He can't go west?
你把电影结尾给换了 哥们
You just switched movies at the end there, bro.
这关乎梦想 我们可不是梦想的毁灭者
It's about a dream, and we are not dream crushers,
比如某些金发女郎  -你的大拇指怎么了?
Like some blonde ladies. What are you doing with your thumb?
我在玩拇指乒乓   -我看出来了
I'm thumb-pong. I can see it.
大伙 好消息 我刚找到了我的灵感篮子
Guys, great news! I found my inspiration basket!
我不知道该担心的是你有这个篮子，还是
I don't know what's more upsetting--that you have one
担心你给篮子起了这个名字
Or that you call it that.
这里面有我所有关于餐馆的创意
It's got all my restaurant ideas and my menus
和我多年收集的菜谱 还有我的计划清单
That I've collected over the years, to-do lists.
"换发型" 也许我会的
"Get haircut." maybe I will,
戴夫于2007年写 也许我会的
2007 Dave. Maybe I will.
你们有什么要说的么?
Anything you guys wanna say?
没有 -没有 哥们 祝你剪出个好发型
Nope. Uh, no, just good luck with that haircut, bro.
谢了 -我说 我会跟他好好谈的
Thanks. Look, I'll talk some sense into him,
到时候他就会明白了
and he'll get it,
戴夫和我永远都是好朋友
All right? Dave and I have been friends forever.
我们俩在一个波段上
We're on the same brave-length.
波段
Brave-length.
是 布拉德 和 戴夫 的波长
It's a Brad and Dave wavelength.
哦 是的
Oh. Yeah.
哦
Oh.
好了 别表现的好像你没有那么解释似地
Okay, don't act like you didn't have to explain that,
那一点用都没用
'cause that made no sense at all.
俩字形容我和 托比 的约会
Two words to describe my date with Toby--ri-dic.
他带我去了一个秘密四角派对
He took me to this secret foursquare party,
那有个乐队
And there was a band made up
是搞说唱的
Entirely of speak & spells.
- 有趣么? - 我觉得是!
- And that was fun? - I think so!
你真的喜欢这个家伙吗 彭?
Are you sure about this guy, pen?
我只是觉得你又回到了以前那种
I just feel like you're doing that thing where you take on
- 故意迎合你喜欢的人的特色的老路上去了 - 我才没有
- The characteristics of the guy you're dating. - I don't do that.
- 嘿! - 嘿!
- Hey! - Hey!
爱情总是会让我们做些疯狂的事情
Love makes us do crazy things.
是么?
Does it?
马科斯 我是真的喜欢他好么?
Max, I really like him, okay?
而你得告诉我该怎么做
And you gotta just tell me what to do
才不会让自己尴尬
So I don't embarrass myself.
好吧 但我所说的每件事你都得照做
Okay, but you've gotta do everything I say.
只能服从 不能有疑问
Follow every direction without asking a single question.
嬉皮士规则一
Hipster rule number one
- 不要尝试 不要努力做任何事 - 了解
- Never try. Never put effort into anything. - Got it.
就随便玩玩就行
Like a flight attendant.
呃 也对
Uh-huh. That's right.
恩 再穿条牛仔裤
Okay, we're gonna need to put jeans under that skirt
再搭配件毛衣
And sweats over those jeans.
规则二，要很能装逼
Hipster rule number two, only like things ironically
书籍 电影 电视 环境
Books, movies, TV shows, the environment.
噢 看看那个
Oh, look at that.
好了 想象你正在和裘 徳洛打乒乓
Okay, you're playing ping-pong against jude law.
啊!
Aah!
你正在和葛伦 克萝丝 一起做咖啡
You're brewing coffee with glenn close.
呃 朋友们 你们知道我在这卖衣服
Uh, guys, you know I sell clothes here--
而且是好衣服?
nice clothes?
阿莱克斯 成年人在说话呢 规则三
Alex, adults are speaking here. Hipster rule number three
永远别显出你很有热情
You can never show too much enthusiasm.
- 这我能做到 - 真的吗?挑战一下 彭
- I can do that. - Can you? Fight it, pen.
不要跳舞 别跳
Don't dance. Don't dance.
她可以跳 看这多有意思啊 别去感受
She can dance. Look how much fun that is. Don't feel it.
看这多有趣啊?
Look how much fun that is.
看我俩玩的多high 告诉我
Look how much fun we're having?tell me?
太有意思了 别跳
Too much--too much fun. Don't dance.
很好 最后一条 所有的事都很愚蠢
Good. Final rule-- everything is dumb.
有人会说一些你不懂的事
Someone says something you don't understand,
你就表现出 "姐才不CARE"
You just go, "I'm over it."
恩 我懂的 我懂的
Froyo. Over it. Other stuff. Over it.
很好 还有一样东西
Great. Just missing one thing.
噢 太漂亮了
Oh, perfect.
去吧，我的小蠢货，小心点，别
Go, my little weirdo. Uh, careful. Don't
看好你的路 - 小心点
Just watch your way. - Please be careful!
恩 那是规定
Yeah. Those are prescript.
噢
Ohh.
我付账
I'll pay for that!
好了 下一项僵尸挑战
All right, next zombie challenge.
拿着它或者
Bring it or bling it.
这不是对吧 僵尸是靠动作感觉的
Not a real phrase. Zombies sense motion,
所以我们要做的是
So what we're gonna do is
谁坐的最久谁赢
Person who sits still the longest wins,
肯定是我赢，因为你是个顶级的傻帽
And that will be me, because you are a type "a" nut job
还没坐性
Who can't sit still.
拜托 这么没水准的游戏
Oh, please. It is on like donkey tron.
我知道你在装着你很有信心
I know you're trying to sound confident,
不过听起来你就像个 50 岁的再婚女人
But you sound like a 50-year-old divorce
和继子说一样
Talking to their stepson.
游戏就要开始 三
Game will begin in three...
二
Two...
一
One.
你想清理那些啤酒的冲动是如此的强烈
you wanna clean up that beer so bad.
才没有
Mnh-mnh.
清理啤酒吧 恩
Clean up the beer. Mmm.
看它们流的到处都是 弄的一团糟
Look at it spilling all over the ground, making a huge mess.
- 天 你必须清理 - 好了!
- God, you gotta clean up - okay!
听着 这不仅一团糟，而且非常危险!
there it is. It is not just messy. It is unsafe!
僵尸已经将你扑到 我把你的身体
Zombies have taken you down, and I am using your body
当做睡袋  典型的骆驼风格
As a sleeping bag, tauntaun style.
顺便说一下，我可不知道那条内裤是谁的
By the way, I have no idea whose boxers those are.
我擦
- Okay.
哦 我知道了，是粉刷匠邻居gary的
Oh, I do. They're gary, the polish neighbor's.
游戏结束了 做饭去吧
Game over and cooked pierogies.
- 你刚才把哪个家伙撞的够呛 - 我觉得
- You ran into that guy really hard back there. - I feel like
我应该完美的将撞击转化成了拥抱
I pretty convincingly turned it into a hug.
哦 嘿 见见我的朋友艾奥尼
Oh, hey, meet my friends ione
和阿迪克斯 - 嘿
and atticus. - Hey.
她有个关于zine的博客
She has a blog about zines,
而他连续三年赢得胡须比赛
And he won the mustache contest three years in a row.
好像哥很在乎一样
like I care.
嘿 看到那个人了么? 他是右撇子
hey, see that guy? He's right-handed,
但他拒绝用他优秀的手弹奏
But he refuses to play with his dominant hand.
哦 那太商业化了
Ohh. It's too commercial.
恩 他在被遗弃的加气站巡回赛可是个巨星
Yeah, he's huge on the abandoned gas station circuit.
你怎么想?
What do you think?
呃
Oh...
不care
Over it.
完全的 恩 ，姐完全不care
Totally. Yeah, I'm so over it right now.
- 恩 我超不care - 我们为啥来这啊?
- Yeah, I'm super over it. - Why are we even here?
鬼知道
I don't know.
首先 欢迎你们 我想向你们介绍
First of all, welcome. I'd like to introduce you
一种改革了的新式芝加哥晚餐
To Chicago's revolutionary new dining experience.
来自世界各地的菜肴
So many cuisines from around the world.
只有一个选择怎么选?
How... Do you choose just one?
你结婚了 是吗 先生?
You're married, right, sir?
恩 和 简 你知道的
Yeah, to Jane. You know that.
假设你俩要出去吃晚餐
Let's say the two of you are going out to dinner,
你想吃墨西哥菜 而她想吃日本菜
And you want Mexican. She wants Japanese.
- 你怎么做? - 那我们就吃日本菜
What do you do? - we get Japanese.
完全正确 没有选择的余地
Exactly. There's no way to decide.
那就是我为什么给你们带来
That's why I give you...
泛大陆烧烤
Pangaea grill.
来自 125 个民族的 900 道菜
900 dishes from 125 ethnic cuisines
都在菜单上了 宝贝
All on one menu, baby.
呃 是啊 看上去有很多
Oh. Right. seems like a lot.
你在复印店花了 17000 美元弄的么?
Did you spend $17,000 at the copy store?
我知道这需要启动资金
And I know this is gonna take capital.
那是我为啥明天
That's why tomorrow I am meeting
要去见一个饭店投资人
With a restaurant investor.
那是重点 伙计们! 我们来庆祝一下!
This is it, guys! Let's celebrate!
泛大陆烧烤 香槟就来了
Pangaea grill. Champ comin'.
怎么回事 布拉德?
What the hell, Brad?
我以为你和 戴夫 谈过了
I thought you talked to Dave.
我得说
I gotta say,
每一次我决定追逐这个梦想
Ever since I decided to pursue this dream again,
我都很兴奋，我以前的世界都是一团漆黑
I'm so happy. I mean, I went to a dark place, man--
但感觉就是黎明前的黑暗
Like applying-to-grad-school dark.
抱歉 你想说些什么?
I'm sorry. What did you wanna talk about?
呃... Hillary clinton（克林顿总统的夫人）
Uh... Hillary clinton--
我给她投票了 我还没给任何说呢
I voted for her. I never told anybody that.
跟人说一说真的很爽
Feels really good to get it off my chest.
中途有点小故障
There was a glitch in the brave-length.
好吧 总得有人要和他谈谈
- Okay, someone needs to talk to him.
当然，不然他就要在芝加哥卖土著民鲸鱼墨西哥卷
Yes, before he starts feeding chicago inuit blubber tacos.
那么 肯定不能是我
Well, it can't be me.
这一年我几乎都毁了他的私人生活
I've already crushed his entire personal life this year.
我可不能在毁掉他的事业
I cannot blow up his professional life.
我现在生活还没支点呢
I'm not at a point right now in my life
- 我又去哪找呢 - 好了 呃 必须有人
- Where I can be taken seriously. - Okay, well, somebody has got
- 和他谈谈 这是必须的 - 戴夫!嘿!
- To talk to him. This is absolutely - Dave! Hey!
- 阿莱 帮我一下? - 恩 当然
- Al, can yohelp me? - Yeah, sure.
伙计们 我真的得谢谢你们的支持
Guys, I wanna thank you for your support.
要知道 没有你们的信任
You know, I couldn't do this without ya.
我是做不到的 套用缅甸的俗话说
Thank you for believing in me, or as they say in burmese...
叽里大呱啦
Kyeizu tin ba de.
好了 香槟献给我真诚的朋友
All right. Champagne for my real friends,
伤害留给我虚伪的朋友
Real pain for my sham friends.
为了 泛大陆
To Pangaea.
为了泛大陆  泛大陆
To Pangaea. Pangaea.
泛大陆
Pangaea.
- 冒泡了 - 泛大陆
- bubble. - Pangaea.
你在我脑中弄的公寓怎么样了 哈?
How's the condo you're building in my brain now, huh?
那是什么? 干得太快导致经济崩溃了吗?
What's that? You built it too quick and the economy collapsed?
而现在你不得不上街去以出卖体力为生
And now you're out on the street doing hand stuff for food,
还有 哦!怎么又是平局?
And--ohh! How do we tie?
又是 2 比 2?
2-2 again?
好了 好了 在这次的僵尸比赛中
Okay, okay. There is one category left
还有一项没有比 那就是比谁更无情
In this zombie-athalon-- ruthlessness.
但我还没想到怎么做
But I haven't figured out how to measure that.
哦 打劫婴儿
Oh. Mug a baby.
当然不是，不过方向是对的
No. But you're in the right area.
嘿 伙计们 想在周五晚上去参加 托比 和
Hey, guys, you wanna come to a super fun party
他朋友的有趣的聚会吗?
On Friday night with Toby and all his friends?
- 不去 - 是很正常的聚会
- No way. - It's gonna be totally normal.
才不是
No, it's not.
好吧 它的主题其实是长岛90年代的成人礼
Fine. it's long island '90s Bat Mitzvah theme.
呃，嬉皮士
Ugh. Hipsters.
你不会觉得烦么?
Aren't you getting a little tired of this?
我是说 总是那些衣服 古老的游戏
I mean, the clothes, the antique yo-yos.
你那个绳子已经弄了四个小时了
You've been making lanyards for four hours.
看上去有好多事要做
Just seems like a lot of work.
有什么恋情是不需要努力的呢?
What relationship isn't work?
阿弗莱克和加雷，他们的娃应该会想出来的
Affleck and garner. Those kids got it figured out.
好了 我承认
Okay, yes.
认识什么是酷的  什么不酷真的很累人
Knowing what's cool and what's not cool is exhausting.
但我正在学习 而且托比也值得我为他这么做
But I'm learning and Toby's worth it.
星期五来嘛就当为我?
Come on Friday for me? There's gonna be
而且派对后还有个拇指摔跤锦标赛
A thumb wrestling tournament at the after-party.
他们中有成年人吗?
Are any of these people adults?
成年礼之后他们就是了嘛
They will be after the bat mitzvah.
想想看吧 时间的起源遇上美食的未来
Imagine the beginning of time meets the future of food,
那就是 老兄...
And that, my good man...
泛大陆烧烤
Is Pangaea grill.
同一个世界 同一个餐馆 --
One world. One restaurant.
真是难以置信
Incredible.
我得打电话叫我的合伙人过来
I have to call my partners in here.
-棒极了 -等他们来了 你再演示一遍
-Great. -And when they get here, pitch it again.
-没问题 -一模一样的
-Okay. -Same way.
-没问题 -就假装你不知道
-Okay. -As if you don't know
这是我听过的最傻逼的点子
It's the stupidest idea I've ever heard.
好的 你说什么?
Okay. What?
我这回错大了
I made a big mistake.
-你不应该怪自己 -没 没 我没有
-You can't blame yourself. -No, no, I'm not.
你懂的 我知道了 经济不景气
You know, I get it. Economy's bad, which is why
我要绕开传统的找投资人这条路
I'm gonna bypass the whole traditional investor thing
自己出钱
And cash in on my 401(k).
另外 和我一起干活的伙计告诉我
Plus I'm working with this guy who told me a way
我可以向他爸借点钱 听起来还行 对不?
I can get a little cash from his dad. Sounds sketchy, right?
大错特错 我需要做的就是带一盒名片
Wrong. All I gotta do is take a box of calling cards
去印第安纳的飞机场
To an airfield in Indiana.
水到渠成
Cut and dry.
嗯
Ahem.
怎么啦?
What's wrong?
想要淡啤酒?
Light beer?
好吧 你们不相信我的烧烤王国计划?
Okay, you don't--don't believe in this whole Pangaea thing?
我热爱餐馆
I love restaurants.
我们--我们都喜欢...餐馆
We--we--we all love... Restaurants.
是啊 我懂了 我懂了
Yeah, I get it. I get it.
戴夫 别走嘛--嗯
Dave, come--ugh.
好吧 这件事的确很棘手
Well, this is officially out of hand,
你们都不想跟他说点什么吗? 真的?
And none of you guys is gonna say anything? Really?
这是淡啤酒
It is light beer.
好吧 我来
Fine. I'll do it.
这都是因为
And this all started as
你们一开始说"谁能在僵尸大战中幸存下来"
Your standard "Who would survive the zombie apocalypse?" debate.
你们能想象如果我们真的
Can you imagine what would happen
开始一场谈话会怎么样?
If we ever had a real conversation?
嘿
Hey.
我懂的 烧烤王国是个蠢毙了的点子
I know. Pangaea was a stupid idea.
不啊...也不全是
No, not... Totally.
就是...
Just...
有很多很蠢的细节
Had a lot of stupid stuff surrounding it.
戴夫 我知道你觉得我是个"梦想粉碎机"
Dave, I know that you think that I'm a dream crusher,
但是这一次 我只想成为"梦想压缩机"
But in this case, I just wanna be a dream compactor.
这样...梦想
Like... Dreams.
好吧 这不公平
Okay, that's not fair.
你的手势让"压缩"都变得可爱了 那么..
The hand gestures make compacting look adorable, so...
这个庞大的计划不适合你 好吧?
This huge scheme is not you, okay?
你又理智又负责任
You're reasonable and responsible.
我知道 我又理智 又负责任
I know. I'm so reasonable and I'm so responsible,
都快把我变成个僵尸了
It turned me into a zombie.
我心里非常明白
All right? I got that message loud and clear.
但是 看嘛
Okay, but look,
这有个折中的办法
There's a middle ground.
你没必要从零突然加速到六十码...
You don't need to go from zero to 60 in...
随便吧 我不懂开车那玩意儿
Whatever. I-I don't know car stuff.
听着 你不需要寿司 你不需要哈萨克小吃
Look, you don't need sushi. You don't need Kazak food.
你没必要取悦素食主义者
You don't need to try and make the Vegans happy.
他们永远不会开心的 做牛肉三明治 好吗?
They never will be. Steak sandwich, okay?
发挥你的特长 从小事做起
Stick with what you're good at. Start small.
或许一间小小的三明治店铺
A little sandwich shop, maybe.
还是得贷点款
-Still need to find some money.
你在向我求婚?
Are you proposing to me?
因为我觉得我俩有段诡异的过去
'cause I feel like we have a weird history.
你原来说过我可以留着它
I know you said that I could keep it,
但是现在我想还给你，虽然不能完全的弥补一切
But I want you to have it. It's not gonna cover everything,
-这只是个开始 -谢谢你 阿莱
-But it's a start. -Thanks, Al.
嘿 可以管我的店子叫"今夜牛排带回家"
Hey, I can call my shop "steak me home tonight."
-不 你不能这么叫 -好吧
-No, you can't do that. -Okay.
我觉得你这么穿可不怎么残忍 简
You don't look very ruthless to me, Jane.
因为穿高跟鞋可跑不过僵尸
Can't outrun a zombie in those heels.
高中的时候 我穿高跟鞋打败过一个女生
In high school, I beat up a girl in these heels.
诺艾尔就不该踩你
Noelle should have never stepped to you
要是她想保留那一块头发的话
If she didn't wanna lose that hunk of hair.
-谢谢大伙捧场... -看我的卷发
-You guys, thank you so much...  for coming! -Watch the crimp.
真不错 跟我来看九十年代的犹太成年礼吧
You look amazing. Let's get this '90s Bat Mitzvah on.
太疯狂了!
It's gonna be insanity!
哦 这没人盛装打扮啊
Uh, no one here's dressed up.
我真是超爱我的决定
I am super happy with my choices.
哦 鱼丸~
Ooh, gefilte fish.
你们花了不少心思打扮吧
You guys seem to be putting in a lot of effort.
没错 为了这个90年代成年礼我们花了不少时间打扮
Yeah, we're just dressed for a '90s Bat Mitzvah.
是啊 卷发 犹太小帽 再明显不过了
Yeah, crimped hair, yarmulke. Seems a little obvious.
明显吗? 为化妆舞会打扮下不应该吗?
Obvious? To be dressing up for a costume party?
嗯 这是个主题派对 是不一样的
Um, this is a theme party. The's a difference.
听着 打扮得太过了一点也不好
Look, it's just not cool to try so hard.
我们太过了?
We are trying too hard?
艾奥尼到哪都带着个空腰包
Ione wears an empty fanny pack everywhere.
阿迪克斯每个周末都在二手市场
Atticus spends his weekends at yard sales
到处找牛仔短裤
Scrounging around for jeans shorts,
而且他还叫阿迪克斯 我还看到你带耳麦了
Plus his name is Atticus. I've seen you wearing headphones
但是根本什么都没插
That aren't attached to anything.
还有这个女孩子坐在个假轮椅上
And this girl is in a fake wheelchair.
我真的出了一场严重的车祸好吧
I was in a really serious accident.
哦 老天 抱歉
Oh, my god. I'm so sorry.
开玩笑的 我活蹦乱跳的 轮椅不错吧?
J.K. I can totes walk. Cool chair, th, right?
好吧，老娘受够了
Okay, that's it.
去死吧你
You're done. Whoa.
听着 各位嬉皮士
listen up, hipsters.
没错 也许我是打扮的太过了
yeah, maybe I do try too hard.
没问题吧? 因为我们这么打扮会很有乐趣
Okay? But that's because trying hard can be fun,
你们这些人知道还有什么很有趣吗?
And you know what else is fun?
真真正正喜欢点什么东西
Actually liking things,
就像这首歌 姐喜欢，非常喜欢
Like this song. I like this song. I like it a lot.
不是讽刺你们 姐就喜欢
Not ironically. I like it, like it,
我的朋友也一样 伙计们 舞起来
And so do my friends. Guys, we're dancing out.
这一点也不难为情
This is not awkward.
好了 好了
You' done. Yeah, okay.
跳得好 注意脚下 晚安
Okay. You're good. The legs. Night.
哦 小吃车 谢天谢地 姐要饿死了
Oh, a food truck. Thank god. I'm starving.
-是啊 我也是的 -哦 饿死我了
-Yeah, me, too. -Oh, I'm hungry.
戴夫?
David?
这是你的吗? 太拉风了!
Is this yours? It's awesome!
我知道 我...听取了某人很好的一个建议
I know. I... Got some really good advice
决定从小餐馆做起
From a special person and decided to start small.
你是说我俩 兄弟
It's all about the brave-length, brother.
不 不 不是说你 嗯 是阿莱克斯
No, no, not you. Uh, Alex.
所以我还不打算辞职
So I'm not gonna quit my job.
-这个餐车就是个兼职 -餐车现在很火
-I'm just gonna do this part-time. -Food trucks are huge right now.
这个餐车真是太正点了 虽然不能开
This thing is awesome, although I cannot drive it.
来的路上我肯定撞上什么东西了
I definitely hit something on the way over here.
撞了个人? 还是个木头? 或者是头猛兽?
Was it a man? Was it a log? Was it a beast?
我们不得而知
We'll never know.
嘿 兄弟们 是餐车也!
Hey, guys, food truck!
嘿 嬉皮士也喜欢小吃车
Hey, hipsters love food trucks.
老兄 我现在还没吃的
Dude, I don't have any food.
-什么? -哦 他们可不喜欢这样
-What? -Ooh, they're not gonna like that.
我可不能失去我最大的客户群
Well, I can't lose my biggest consumer base.
他们会在网上给我差评的
They'll tweet me out of business.
大家都上车 马科斯你去引开那些人
Everybody get in the truck. Max, you distract the hipsters.
嘿 帅哥! 看那边!
Hey, everybody! Look over there!
索菲亚 科波拉在那边打羽毛球
Sofia Coppola's playing badminton
跟杰森 施沃茨曼 一起!
With Jason Schwartzman!
开车! 开车!
Drive! Drive!
刚刚在那些嬉皮士面前表现不错嘛
Impressive moves back there with those hipsters.
或许我们都能打赢僵尸大战
Maybe we'd both do oka in a zombie apocalypse.
开玩笑? 只要我们联合起来
Are you kidding? With our skills combined,
-我们就能战无不胜 -哦 一大波僵尸来了
-We'd be unstoppable. -Oh, there's more of 'em.
什么? 哦!
What? Ow!
冷酷无情! 哇!
Ruthlessness! Whoo!
好的 真够哥们
all right, okay. Very funny, guys.
把你们的朋友扔到路边 开慢点
Throw your friend out of a car. Slow down.
戴夫 开慢点 我不能跑步 人家还没热身
Dave, slow down. I can't run. I didn't stretch today,
别--停下来 完了 腿抽筋了 戴夫
So don't--slow down. All right, pulled my hamstring, Dave.
戴夫 人家腿抽筋了! 慢点!
Dave, I pulled my hammy out! Slow down!
另一条腿也抽筋了! 另一条腿也抽筋了!
I pulled my other hamstring out! I pulled my other hamstring out!
戴夫! 戴夫 你是--
Dave! Dave, you're--
太不够朋友了!
This is not something that friends do to each other!
人家腿抽筋了!
I have a cramp!